Subtitle Provide by dramacool.in Translator [Admin.@YNG]
تم توفير الترجمة بواسطة مترجم dramacool.in [Admin.@YNG]
[Kim Kangmin as Choi Siyeol]
[كيم كانجمين في دور تشوي سيول]
[KEVIN as Na Aejoon]
[كيفن في دور نا أيجون]
[Byunghun as Yeon Jooha]
[بيونغ هون في دور يون جوها]
[Kim Hongjun as Ji Kyusung]
[كيم هونغجون في دور جي كيوسونغ]
[My Bias is Showing?!]
[تحيزي يظهر؟!]
It's my first time filming a variety show, so there were quite a few mistakes.
إنها المرة الأولى التي أقوم فيها بتصوير برنامج منوعات، لذا كان هناك بعض الأخطاء.
I wonder if I've caused any trouble for everyone.
أتساءل عما إذا كنت قد تسببت في أي مشكلة للجميع.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
What are you sorry for?
لماذا أنت آسف؟
It's my first time, too.
وهذه المرة الأولى لي أيضاً.
I'm really nervous, too.
أنا متوترة حقا أيضا.
Would a professional like you be nervous, too?
هل يمكن لمحترف مثلك أن يشعر بالتوتر أيضًا؟
That's interesting.
هذا ممتع.
It's the first recording today.
إنه التسجيل الأول اليوم.
If everything goes smoothly today,
إذا سارت الأمور بسلاسة اليوم،
shall we fulfil each other's wishes?
هل نحقق رغبات بعضنا البعض؟
W-Wish?
W-Wish؟
Is there anything you'd like me to do?
هل هناك أي شيء تريد مني أن أفعله؟
I...
أنا...
I do have one.
لدي واحدة.
You will...
سوف تفعلها...
agree to it, right?
موافق على ذلك، أليس كذلك؟
We'll be together for a few more weeks.
سوف نكون معًا لعدة أسابيع أخرى.
Let's get closer.
دعونا نقترب.
Siyeol, how much longer do you need?
سييول، كم من الوقت تحتاجين؟
I'm done.
أنا انتهيت.
As for your wish, just tell me when you've decided.
أما بالنسبة لرغبتك، فقط أخبرني عندما تقرر.
In that case...
في هذه الحالة...
Could I trouble you to take a photo?
هل يمكنني أن أطلب منك التقاط صورة؟
I-I want to show off to my friends that I'm filming a show.
أريد أن أظهر لأصدقائي أنني أقوم بتصوير عرض.
You can take as many as you want.
يمكنك أن تأخذ العدد الذي تريده.
Shall we go look for the intern teacher?
هل نذهب للبحث عن المعلم المتدرب؟
Cut. Okay.
قطع.حسنا.
Mr. Na, you look much better now.
السيد نا، أنت تبدو أفضل بكثير الآن.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Mr. Na, give us a moment as we check this scene.
السيد نا، امنحنا لحظة بينما نتحقق من هذا المشهد.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
[Episode 3: My Bias Texted Me?]
[الحلقة 3: هل أرسل لي تحيزي رسالة نصية؟]
[Choi Siyeol]
[تشوي سيول]
I feel like I've crossed the line.
أشعر وكأنني تجاوزت الحد.
I mean, I got to meet him in person,
أعني، لقد التقيت به شخصيا،
and on top of that, I got his number, too?
وعلاوة على ذلك، حصلت على رقمه أيضًا؟
I want to contact him...
أريد التواصل معه...
I want to hear his voice...
أريد أن أسمع صوته...
Siyeol's voice from the other end of the phone call...
صوت سيول من الطرف الآخر للمكالمة الهاتفية...
[Choi Siyeol]
[تشوي سيول]
Please let me listen to it once.
أرجو أن تسمح لي بالاستماع إليه مرة واحدة.
No. Come to your senses, Na Aejoon!
لا. تعال إلى رشدك، نا أيجون!
Are you going to call him and say that you're a fan?
هل ستتصل به وتقول له أنك من المعجبين؟
But...
لكن...
this is a once-in-a-lifetime chance...
هذه فرصة تأتي مرة واحدة في العمر...
[Continue acting like you're not a fan] [Reveal that you're a fan and become a successful one]
[استمر في التصرف وكأنك لست من المعجبين] [اكشف أنك من المعجبين وكن واحدًا ناجحًا]
This Siyeol I think about all the time is right in front of my eyes!
[أظهر أنك من المعجبين وكن من المعجبين الناجحين]
[Continue acting like you're not a fan]
[استمر في التصرف وكأنك لست من المعجبين]
[Reveal that you're a fan and become a successful one]
[اكشف أنك من المعجبين وكن واحدًا ناجحًا]
But my contract is about to be renewed.
لكن عقدي على وشك أن يتم تجديده.
If this is exposed...
إذا تم الكشف عن هذا...
[Continue acting like you're not a fan]
[استمر في التصرف وكأنك لست من المعجبين]
[Reveal that you're a fan and become a successful one]
[اكشف أنك من المعجبين وكن واحدًا ناجحًا]
I can go for more interviews, but Siyeol...
أستطيع أن أذهب لإجراء المزيد من المقابلات، ولكن سييول...
[Reveal that you're a fan and become a successful one]
[أظهر أنك من المعجبين وكن من المعجبين الناجحين]
Siyeol won't appear again!
سييول لن يظهر مرة أخرى!
[Continue acting like you're not a fan] [Reveal that you're a fan and become a successful one]
[استمر في التصرف وكأنك لست من المعجبين] [اكشف أنك من المعجبين وكن واحدًا ناجحًا]
Siyeol might be very uncomfortable.
قد يكون سييول غير مرتاح للغاية.
He thinks I'm not a fan.
يعتقد أنني لست من المعجبين.
Wait.
انتظر.
He asked me for my contact.
لقد طلب مني التواصل معه.
[Reveal that you're a fan and become a successful one]
[أظهر أنك من المعجبين وكن من المعجبين الناجحين]
Do I have to be so cautious?
هل يجب علي أن أكون حذرا إلى هذه الدرجة؟
But still...
ولكن لا يزال...
I'm scared to go back to being unemployed.
أنا خائفة من العودة إلى البطالة.
I saw a student reading other books during class,
رأيت طالبًا يقرأ كتبًا أخرى أثناء الدرس،
so I scolded them a little.
لذلك وبختهم قليلا.
Mr. Na Aejoon.
السيد باي ايجون.
Why do you think the school hired someone like you
لماذا تعتقد أن المدرسة وظفت شخصًا مثلك؟
with no good educational background or experience?
بدون خلفية تعليمية أو خبرة جيدة؟
Huh?
هاه؟
You won't stand out if your abilities are just average.
لن تبرز إذا كانت قدراتك متوسطة فقط.
Whatever you do, just don't stand out.
مهما فعلت، فقط لا تبرز.
Stay quiet like you are now
ابقى هادئًا كما أنت الآن
and just fill the seat.
وملء المقعد فقط.
Understand?
يفهم؟
Yes, I got it.
نعم لقد حصلت عليه.
I think it's better
أعتقد أنه أفضل
to keep it as it is right now.
للحفاظ على الأمر كما هو الآن.
[Just like the scent of spring carried in on a breeze]
[تمامًا مثل رائحة الربيع التي يحملها النسيم]
Just like the scent of spring carried in on a breeze...
تمامًا مثل رائحة الربيع التي يحملها النسيم...
[Like a heat haze that briefly rises and then disappears...]
[مثل ضباب الحرارة الذي يرتفع لفترة وجيزة ثم يختفي ...]
Like a heat haze that briefly rises and then disappears...
مثل ضباب الحرارة الذي يرتفع لفترة وجيزة ثم يختفي ...
Just like that.
هكذا فقط.
What are you muttering in the room alone?
ماذا تتمتم في الغرفة وحدك؟
Sounded like you were performing a ritual...
يبدو الأمر وكأنك كنت تؤدي طقوسًا ...
I ordered fried chicken.
طلبت دجاج مقلي.
Come out and eat.
تعالوا وتناولوا الطعام.
Fried chicken?
دجاج مقلي؟
Did you make things clear when you
هل أوضحت الأمور عندما قلت ذلك؟
broke up with me on your own accord?
انفصلت عني بمحض إرادتك؟
That's because...
هذا لأن...
[If I were to tell you it's because I didn't want to implicate you...]
[إذا قلت لك ذلك لأنني لا أريد أن أتورط معك ...]
You have a... new boyfriend, right?
لديك صديق جديد، أليس كذلك؟
You'd try to reconcile.
ستحاول التوفيق.
Yeah.
نعم.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Why did you order supper?
لماذا طلبت العشاء؟
Well.
حسنًا.
I just feel empty inside.
أشعر بالفراغ في داخلي.
What about you?
ماذا عنك؟
You even left me with your bank account.
حتى أنك تركتني مع حسابك البنكي.
You're still breathing.
أنت لا تزال تتنفس.
Do you know what this is?
هل تعرف ما هذا؟
What is it?
ما هذا؟
Siyeol's phone number.
رقم هاتف سيول.
We exchanged contact numbers today.
لقد قمنا بتبادل أرقام الاتصال اليوم.
What?
ماذا؟
He gave you his phone number?
هل أعطاك رقم هاتفه؟
Yes.
نعم.
Personally.
شخصيا.
He's acting strange.
إنه يتصرف بغرابة.
Darn it.
لعنة عليك.
That's why you were acting like you were performing a ritual?
لهذا السبب كنت تتصرف وكأنك تقوم بطقوس؟
No.
لا.
But... I've decided to face reality.
ولكن... قررت مواجهة الواقع.
I can't just think about the present now.
لا أستطيع أن أفكر في الحاضر فقط الآن.
I like him,
انا احبه
but what I have today took time to build.
لكن ما لدي اليوم استغرق وقتًا لبنائه.
I'm determined not to let all this fall apart.
لقد قررت أن لا أسمح لكل هذا أن ينهار.
Aejoon, Kota Kinabalu is so pretty.
إيجون، كوتا كينابالو جميلة جدًا.
[Aejoon, Kota Kinabalu is so pretty.]
[إيجون، كوتا كينابالو جميلة جدًا.]
This darn Kota Kinabalu!
هذه كوتا كينابالو اللعينة!
Determined, as if.
مصمم، كما لو.
You reacted so quickly.
لقد كان رد فعلك سريعًا جدًا.
Hey!
يا!
That's not true.
هذا ليس صحيحا.
I really decided to give up!
لقد قررت فعلا الاستسلام!
Oh... Look at this.
أوه... انظر إلى هذا.
Me aside,
أنا جانبا،
what's with you?
ماذا بك؟
Are you waiting for someone's call?
هل تنتظر اتصال من أحد؟
What are you talking about? No.
عن ماذا تتحدث؟ لا.
Look at you. It's like you're waiting for a text
انظر إليك. يبدو الأمر كما لو كنت تنتظر رسالة نصية.
from someone you've broken up with.
من شخص انفصلت عنه.
[Did he really perform a ritual?]
[هل قام فعلاً بأداء طقوس؟]
Do you have any other clothes?
هل لديك أي ملابس أخرى؟
[Give-up Look]
[نظرة الاستسلام]
Other clothes?
ملابس اخرى؟
No, I don't have any.
لا، ليس لدي أي شيء.
Oh, gosh...
أوه، يا إلهي...
Do we have outfits for him?
هل لدينا ملابس له؟
I can't let you wear sportswear either...
لا أستطيع أن أسمح لك بارتداء الملابس الرياضية أيضًا...
Siyeol, you're here.
سييول، أنت هنا.
Can we start the recording immediately?
هل يمكننا البدء بالتسجيل فورًا؟
We'll be right back.
سوف نعود قريبا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
What's going on?
ماذا يحدث هنا؟
Did something happen?
هل حدث شيء؟
Oh. Hyeonwoo!
أوه. هيونوو!
Yes?
نعم؟
Come over for a bit.
تعالوا قليلا.
Do you have extra clothes?
هل لديك ملابس اضافية؟
I do have Siyeol's.
لدي سييول.
Just once. Just lend it to us.
مرة واحدة فقط. فقط أقرضها لنا.
No, it's sponsored.
لا، إنه برعاية.
It's been worn before. Is that okay?
لقد تم ارتداؤه من قبل. هل هذا مناسب؟
That's fine. That'd be great.
لا بأس، سيكون ذلك رائعًا.
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
Mr. Na.
السيد سو.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Get changed first.
قم بالتغيير أولاً.
After the recording, you can go there
بعد التسجيل يمكنك الذهاب إلى هناك
and return it to that manager.
وإعادته إلى ذلك المدير.
Okay.
تمام.
This is Siyeol's clothes.
هذه ملابس سييول.
How could I... It's so precious...
كيف يمكنني... إنه ثمين للغاية...
It smells so good.
رائحتها طيبة جداً.
Quiet down.
هدوء.
While all of you should already know,
في حين أنكم جميعا يجب أن تعرفوا بالفعل،
let me introduce him officially.
دعوني أقدمه رسميًا.
This is Mr. Choi Siyeol
هذا هو السيد تشوي سيول
who'll be an intern teacher at our school
من سيكون مدرسًا متدربًا في مدرستنا؟
for the next few weeks.
للأسابيع القليلة القادمة.
Hello.
مرحبًا.
I'm the Korean language teacher, Choi Siyeol.
أنا مدرس اللغة الكورية، تشوي سي يول.
So handsome.
وسيم جداً.
Siyeol's face that I always see in videos...
وجه سيول الذي أراه دائمًا في الفيديوهات...
A familiar face...
وجه مألوف...
Where were we last time?
أين كنا في المرة الماضية؟
Tell us about your first love!
أخبرنا عن حبك الأول!
Well...
حسنًا...
Hey!
يا!
Why are you asking about first love stories during class time?
لماذا تسأل عن قصص الحب الأولى أثناء وقت الدرس؟
You're making Mr. Choi uncomfortable.
أنت تجعل السيد تشوي غير مرتاح.
H-How could you ask that?
ح-كيف يمكنك أن تسأل ذلك؟
Seriously.
بجد.
Would you mind sharing with us, Mr. Choi?
هل تمانع في مشاركتنا، السيد تشوي؟
Oh, my first love?
أوه حبي الأول؟
I think it was when I was 18.
أعتقد أن ذلك كان عندما كان عمري 18 عامًا.
That was when I was the most anxious, nervous, and tired.
لقد كان ذلك عندما كنت في أقصى درجات القلق والتوتر والتعب.
There was a group of people who'd give me one-sided support.
كانت هناك مجموعة من الأشخاص الذين قدموا لي الدعم من جانب واحد.
It's our...
إنها...
A Want You.
أريدك.
Oh? I mean it.
أوه؟ أنا أعني ذلك.
I like them the most.
انا احبهم اكثر من غيرهم.
I love them now.
انا احبهم الان.
-[Want Yous love you more, Siyeol.] -Shall we start the class?
-[أريد أن أحبك أكثر، سيول.] -هل نبدأ الدرس؟
-Yes.
-نعم.
You can start the class from here.
يمكنك البدء في الدرس من هنا.
Okay.
تمام.
Mr. Choi will read you some materials.
السيد تشوي سوف يقرأ لك بعض المواد.
Listen carefully.
استمع بعناية.
-Yes.
-نعم.
In a birch forest filled with nameless flowers,
في غابة البتولا المليئة بالزهور التي لا اسم لها،
I recalled a memory.
لقد تذكرت ذكرى.
The old woman who lived in the cabin said,
قالت المرأة العجوز التي كانت تسكن في الكابينة:
"Even a single gust of wind,
"حتى عاصفة واحدة من الرياح،
a blade of grass,
شفرة من العشب،
or a drop of dew—
أم قطرة ندى؟؟؟
everything has a reason for its existence."
"لكل شيء سبب لوجوده."
The grandmother would often stop on the path.
وكانت الجدة تتوقف في كثير من الأحيان على الطريق.
She would then quietly stroke a still stone and say,
ثم تقوم بهدوء بمسح الحجر الساكن وتقول،
"This stone supports someone's path
"هذا الحجر يدعم طريق شخص ما
or helps rainwater flow."
"أو يساعد على تدفق مياه الأمطار."
Okay, that's all for today.
حسنًا، هذا كل شيء لهذا اليوم.
Let's applaud for today's intern teacher.
دعونا نحيي المعلم المتدرب اليوم.
Don't forget to do your homework.
لا تنسى أن تقوم بواجباتك المنزلية.
Remember to hand it in.
تذكر أن تسلّمه.
-Yes!
-نعم!
Mr. Choi, come to our class next time too!
السيد تشوي، تعال إلى صفنا في المرة القادمة أيضًا!
Let's go.
دعنا نذهب.
-Good job. -Siyeol.
-عمل جيد. -سيول.
You did a really good job.
لقد قمت بعمل جيد حقًا.
Ah... Yes.
أه... نعم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Mr. Choi, can we take a photo together?
السيد تشوي، هل يمكننا التقاط صورة معًا؟
I'm sorry. We're busy.
انا آسف. نحن مشغولون.
Let's do it next time.
دعونا نفعل ذلك في المرة القادمة.
-I'm sorry.
-أنا آسف.
Get back to studying.
العودة للدراسة.
-Yes.
-نعم.
The atmosphere is different.
الجو مختلف .
Did something happen?
هل حدث شيء؟
You said you wanted to try the cafeteria.
قلت أنك تريد تجربة الكافتيريا.
How is it?
كيف هذا؟
It's really good.
إنه جيد حقا.
Especially this. This is my favorite.
هذا هو المفضل لدي.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Eat more, our baby.
تناولي المزيد، يا صغيرتي.
When I was a kid,
عندما كنت طفلا،
-my mum made this for me a lot... -Hold on.
- أمي صنعت هذا من أجلي كثيرًا... -انتظر.
Let us change the memory card.
دعونا نغير بطاقة الذاكرة.
Is this enough?
هل هذا كافي؟
Take more off.
خذ المزيد من الراحة.
Again?
مرة أخرى؟
That unfamiliar face.
هذا الوجه غير المألوف.
Have some.
خذ بعضًا منها.
Okay, let's continue the filming.
حسنًا، لنستمر في التصوير.
Choi Siyeol, Mr. Na, can we start filming now?
تشوي سيول، السيد نا، هل يمكننا أن نبدأ التصوير الآن؟
Okay, action.
حسنا، العمل.
Do the teachers come and eat at the cafeteria every day?
هل يأتي المعلمون لتناول الطعام في الكافتيريا كل يوم؟
Huh?
هاه؟
Yes, there are days like that,
نعم، هناك أيام مثل تلك،
and there are days where we eat out.
وهناك أيام نتناول فيها الطعام خارج المنزل.
But...
لكن...
this sausage is the best.
هذه النقانق هي الأفضل.
It's your first time experiencing being an intern teacher.
إنها المرة الأولى التي تختبر فيها تجربة أن تكون مدرسًا متدربًا.
How do you feel?
ما هو شعورك؟
To be honest, I was worried.
لأكون صادقا، كنت قلقا.
But thanks to Mr. Na's gentle guidance,
ولكن بفضل التوجيه اللطيف للسيد نا،
it was a really fun experience.
لقد كانت تجربة ممتعة حقًا.
But you're so good that it didn't look like it was your first time.
لكنك جيد جدًا لدرجة أن الأمر لم يبدو كما لو كانت المرة الأولى لك.
Really?
حقًا؟
He somehow feels... unfamiliar.
إنه يشعر بطريقة ما بأنه... غير مألوف.
The first day of "Go! School Teacher" has wrapped up successfully.
انتهى اليوم الأول من برنامج "انطلق يا معلم المدرسة" بنجاح.
I'll get off work for today.
سأغادر العمل اليوم.
See you next time.
نراكم في المرة القادمة.
-Bye.
-وداعا وداعا.
Cut. Okay.
قطع.حسنا.
Good work.
عمل جيد.
Good job.
أحسنت.
Good work, Siyeol.
عمل جيد، سييول.
Yes.
نعم.
Good work.
عمل جيد.
Mr. Choi, this is for you.
السيد تشوي، هذا لك.
Mr. Choi, you're so handsome.
السيد تشوي، أنت وسيم جدًا.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Mr. Na, hold on.
السيد نا، انتظر.
Yes.
نعم.
Let me show you the schedule.
دعني أريك الجدول الزمني.
We need to match the dates.
نحن بحاجة إلى مطابقة التواريخ.
Yes.
نعم.
No matter what, that was a gift from the students...
مهما كان الأمر، كانت تلك هدية من الطلاب...
Oh, right. The clothes!
اوه، صحيح. الملابس!
Things that only happen in dreams keep happening,
الأشياء التي تحدث فقط في الأحلام تستمر في الحدوث،
making me confused.
مما يجعلني مرتبكًا.
We'll be together for a few more weeks.
سوف نكون معًا لعدة أسابيع أخرى.
Let's get closer.
دعونا نقترب.
I got his number, worried all night, and was so dramatic about it.
لقد حصلت على رقمه، وكنت قلقة طوال الليل، وكنت دراماتيكية للغاية بشأن هذا الأمر.
I want to contact him...
أريد التواصل معه...
I want to hear his voice...
أريد أن أسمع صوته...
How embarrassing, Na Aejoon.
كم هو محرج، نا ايجون.
These are all things you don't have to worry about.
هذه كلها أشياء لا داعي للقلق بشأنها.
Ah. Yes.
اه. نعم.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Good work.
عمل جيد.
I knew it.
كنت أعرف.
Fantasies should stay as fantasies.
ينبغي للخيالات أن تبقى مجرد خيالات.
[Stabilizer]
[المثبت]
Good work, Siyeol.
عمل جيد، سييول.
Mm.
مم.
Brother, I need to talk to Ms. Han.
أخي أريد التحدث مع السيدة هان.
I'm afraid it'll take a long time.
أخشى أن يستغرق الأمر وقتا طويلا.
Get in the car first.
ادخل إلى السيارة أولاً.
-Got it. -Okay.
-فهمت. -حسنا.
[Na Aejoon]
[بقلم ايجون]
Hello?
مرحبًا؟
This is Na Aejoon.
هذا هو نا ايجون.
I know.
أنا أعرف.
Go ahead.
تفضل.
I haven't returned the clothes I borrowed.
لم أرجع الملابس التي استعرتها.
Where are you now?
أين أنت الآن؟
Your clothes.
ملابسك.
You could've returned it to me during the next recording.
كان بإمكانك إرجاعه لي أثناء التسجيل التالي.
Even so...
مع ذلك...
Also...
أيضًا...
Here.
هنا.
I saw this in your pocket.
لقد رأيت هذا في جيبك.
I was worried that by acting I didn't see it might upset you.
كنت قلقًا من أنه من خلال التمثيل الذي لم أره قد يزعجك.
Ah...
اه...
Yes.
نعم.
Well. See you during the next recording!
حسناً. نراكم في التسجيل القادم!
Well...
حسنًا...
I thought about not saying this since it could be
لقد فكرت في عدم قول هذا لأنه قد يكون
crossing the line.
عبور الخط.
But you seemed tired during the recording.
لكنك كنت تبدو متعبًا أثناء التسجيل.
During times like that, you could give me a signal.
في مثل هذه الأوقات، يمكنك أن تعطيني إشارة.
What do you mean?
ماذا تقصد؟
Well...
حسنًا...
For example, the fact that you don't eat–
على سبيل المثال، حقيقة أنك لا تأكل؟؟؟
but maybe this is just how you always are.
ولكن ربما هذه هي الطريقة التي أنت عليها دائمًا.
I saw there were times your face turned gloomy during the recording...
لقد رأيت أن هناك أوقاتًا أصبح فيها وجهك قاتمًا أثناء التسجيل ...
If I got it wrong,
إذا أخطأت،
I'm really sorry.
انا آسف حقا.
I said something wrong.
لقد قلت شيئا خاطئا.
Who are you to say that?
من أنت لتقول هذا؟
That's right.
هذا صحيح.
I have neurogenic gastritis.
لدي التهاب المعدة العصبي.
I'm not quite able to eat during recordings.
أنا لست قادراً على تناول الطعام أثناء التسجيلات.
After drinking a spiked drink three years ago,
بعد شرب مشروب مسكر منذ ثلاث سنوات،
the company has set a rule for me to avoid any outside food.
لقد وضعت الشركة لي قاعدة لتجنب تناول أي طعام خارجي.
-Oh, that's why... -But...
-أوه، لهذا السبب... -لكن...
My face turned gloomy at times during the filming
لقد أصبح وجهي كئيبًا في بعض الأحيان أثناء التصوير
was not because of my physical condition.
ولم يكن ذلك بسبب حالتي الجسدية.
Huh?
هاه؟
Well, then it's because...
حسنا، إذن السبب هو...
It's because of
إنه بسبب
Mr. Na Aejoon.
السيد باي ايجون.
Huh?
هاه؟
Did I do something wrong...
هل فعلت شيئا خاطئا...
We exchanged numbers and I even took the initiative to text you.
لقد قمنا بتبادل الأرقام وحتى أنني أخذت زمام المبادرة لإرسال رسالة نصية إليك.
Yet you didn't reply.
ولكنك لم ترد.
Are you
أنت
drawing a line with me?
رسم خط معي؟
Me?
أنا؟
[Choi Siyeol: Please take care of me for today's recording too.]
[تشوي سيول: من فضلك اعتني بي للتسجيل اليوم أيضًا.]
Please take care of me for today's recording too.
من فضلك اعتني بي للتسجيل اليوم أيضًا.
How could I ignore my bias's text...
كيف يمكنني تجاهل نص تحيزي...
I didn't mean to ignore it.
لم أقصد أن أتجاهله.
I might have seen it while I was working and forgot to reply...
ربما رأيته أثناء عملي ونسيت الرد...
Really!
حقًا!
How could I not reply to your messages...
كيف لا أستطيع الرد على رسائلك؟
So...
لذا...
It didn't go as I thought, so I felt really upset and stiffled.
لم يحدث الأمر كما توقعت، لذلك شعرت بالانزعاج الشديد والتصلب.
I couldn't even look at your face all day.
لم أستطع حتى النظر إلى وجهك طوال اليوم.
I mean...
أعني...
Why would someone like you b-be upset because of
لماذا قد ينزعج شخص مثلك بسبب
someone like me?
شخص مثلي؟
This is really...
هذا حقا...
How should I put it?
كيف يجب أن أضعه؟
I-I don't understand.
انا لا افهم.
I'm already making it so clear.
لقد جعلت الأمر واضحًا بالفعل.
Do you still not understand?
هل مازلت لا تفهم؟
You don't seem to hate it though...
لا يبدو أنك تكره ذلك على الرغم من ذلك...
I'm flirting...
أنا أغازل...
with you, Mr. Na Aejoon.
معك السيد نا ايجون.
Since the first time I met you,
منذ المرة الأولى التي التقيتك فيها،
I've been interested
لقد كنت مهتما
in you.
في داخلك.
[In the next episode]
[في الحلقة القادمة]
Kyusung wants to break up.
كيوسونغ يريد الانفصال.
I don't know what to do.
لا أعرف ماذا أفعل.
You can't do this to Jooha.
لا يمكنك فعل هذا لجوها.
We can't do this to Jooha.
لا يمكننا أن نفعل هذا لجوها.
I think he's seeing someone else.
أعتقد أنه يرى شخصًا آخر.
Do you want to meet today?
هل تريد أن نلتقي اليوم؟
I'm very interested
أنا مهتم جدًا
in you.
في داخلك.
Are you... seeing someone?
هل أنت... ترى شخصًا ما؟